ok last chance you smart your
nose clean everything
and when we meditate in a group it is very important
that you do not move then if you
do this you stop you get
karma stopping people in the great garden
directly but you don't want that right
[music]
in these days
your forehead
Yandex
relax the corners of your mouth
loosen your eyelids
cool
relax fingers
and pull in your stomach a little shoulders back a little
and a small smile on your face and please
connect now to the sound of the air conditioner
just fall sound of the air conditioner or
any other sound that you
will now catch in the hall
[music]
and now feel the beating of your heart and
if it is very quiet inside
if it is very quiet around then sometimes you
can catch the beating of your heart but
in a hall like we are now with
so many people it may be
difficult to do ends you can just
feel the beating of your heart in your
chest
be and happily place your consciousness
in your heart if you start to think and that about nothing will be
waiting
than about what happened recently or
something not very pleasant the best
to place from  awareness in the heart, do
n't think about parcel 1
now let's go inside your
heart it's not like a damp place it's a
very comfortable meditation
space with a lot of
sunlight
and you can feel your heart beating
around your eyes
and imagine that now everything your whole
heart inside becomes the shape of a penthouse there are a lot of
rooms a lot of windows and you
go into one of the rooms where there are
no windows and it's a wonderful very
beautiful room for meditation you can still
hear the beating of your heart in the
room that you are now behind the
walls of this room wide open
inside these rooms it's even
quieter even quieter than before
next to me there is 100 I'm lying with
sugar
and with my left hand with the third finger I
will find you before this time scattered
sugar
which I pull out a
small crystal of sugar and
[music]
sticks to the tip of my finger and I
think that I would like to meditate
inside this crystal of zara
and they remained very, very small
[music]
and on one side of this crystal of
sugar a door opens and I go
inside
[music]
and inside this crystal of sugar there
is enough  big
police and a room of
haystacks meditate in this
tiny-tiny little
space
[music]
now this sugar crystal
suddenly emerges the whole Pacific Ocean
[music]
huge tekke of a
very beautiful blue color and very
smooth water
autumn is so quiet
and it touches the shore in China and back the
shores of Mexico California suddenly it starts to rain from the sky
and every drop falls into this Pacific
Ocean
[music]
and on the ocean suddenly waves appear from
one shore to the other everything is covered with
waves and I follow with my consciousness
these waves after one wave after another
then after the next and so on
and now in the sky
[music]
appears such an always blue color
like the sea and a very very high sky
appears
and an endless sky endless sea
find the auction site May May
turn off your consciousness
as if I turn off the light I just
stop thinking
[music]
if thoughts start appearing in my
head I notice
but I stop it there will be
such a small struggle
and peace
now I will go ours even quieter
[music]
to fight the thoughts that pop up and
stop them, it bothers my
consciousness a little rhinestones I will go even deeper
and a quieter space and when
the smear pops up I just
ignore it I will not listen to it I
will not fight it because my
consciousness now completely turns off
quite
now I will think about one of my
teachers
maybe it will be your mom or your dad
who were your teachers
maybe a teacher at school
your be a sports teacher
[music] music
music teacher
maybe in the teacher who helped you in
your work maybe your spiritual
teacher in the wat of life maybe
some priest maybe killed imam
there
maybe it is some historical
figure teacher as a dish or Jesus
fan
your savior exact lama is a very-very
important object for meditation
if you do not have heart teachers yet you have
not found him yet
[music]
then you can just invite your
heart teacher as you
imagine him he will come and will be in front of
you will sit on very beautiful
flowers
will be covered or lotus
and take out and together  meditate
enjoy his beautiful peaceful
face and the feeling of love that will lead to
each other
and now think about the fact that your teacher and the
hook he is created from the seeds in my
consciousness and small pictures come out of
my consciousness and the pictures open up and the
whole picture of my teacher comes out in
my image and these images
create my teacher
and think something about what you
like about your teacher and the quality
that you like your tormentors
maybe how kind he is
to other people
[music]
maybe I was a little like him
we have passed lives
now we are on a journey our past
life just a few minutes and then
we will have a break
[music]
try to imagine a
life passed
when you did some things and
this allowed you to plant the seeds to
see those qualities of the teacher that you
see in my case in my past life
once I was very kind to
other people and now create once
in a movie
use your imagination
maybe and folded somewhere in an Arab country
maybe I was part of an
Arab group maybe I was a tall
woman
very elegant
I always always took care of my people in
my group and create a story that's how this is
all that you can imagine
what can happen  Because of these finals,
any story you create with stitch will not be
true, enjoy, don't
be too serious about it, maybe
more like a bird
that took care of other points, maybe
you were a fish,
go to any country, any place,
and let your consciousness simply
choose pictures of your past life
when you created beautiful incredible
things to plant seeds, betray that
you have just seen such a wonderful
teacher as you have,
or after that, I would like to ask
a few people where they were in their
past lives, and maybe, uh-huh, and
share your stories with us,
good job, let's go
[music]
use your imagination,
enjoy
[music]
now go back to your teacher,
look at his beautiful face, beautiful
smile,
think like in an elevator, what are you like,
and we will now finish with three deep
breaths in and out
[music]
years want clay, and during rest, we
send beautiful seeds of our good
karma,
we place them in the wind that will carry
these seeds to all people,
and now you can gradually open your
eyes,
do some stretching, stretch
[music]
we need a microphone, now it will be  somewhere
minutes to complain I write my phone and
which was left here on the stage with for
recording
[music]
and we will no longer do meditation
this morning
7 are you guys ready with the microphone
[music]
somewhere 10 minutes let's share a
story from your past life okay
[music]
who is trying to control the microphone
you are pushing people just choose yourself
even if they do not raise your hand
it is up to you sometimes they are shy and it
becomes even more interesting if
you are too sensitive and say I
forgot my story it was a long time ago
your story has passed in life right
kiss the microphone okay
I was an American
[music]
I found my purpose in my life
it's all
and the power of good in the morning
I imagined remembering that I
remember
that I was born in 17 fno bibi and my
mom and dad were I I had two
brothers
they are older than me it was a boy and a
girl
I was then the height
I was interested in the fact that I wanted to become a
teacher for children and what actually
happened next
I discovered that I would like to help I would like to
help people and  other leaders
from other villages who showed us
from the edge would not want to help so that their
places where they lived would have more
peace and tranquility and we met
near my house and
shared experiences on how to help each other
[music]
and we
choose
and we shared love and supported
each other in our community it's
cool when in stories your story
please add that this seed
created your life now
[music]
dusty
I remember at the moment when we started
doing this I was just flying somewhere I
opened my eyes and I began to see clouds and
mountains Kopytova I was flying I was trying to understand
where I was and at one point I realized the
tambora itself was as if
my dreams were just passing by
[music]
that is, there was such a state as if in my
opinion there was enough courage to
fly like this before and now it has appeared in me
when I was a child I
was always screaming - something to
go to some strange Asia
and when I got there I just saw that
I was there but I forgot about it and in this
meditation I began to remember about it.
[music]
and that's all because then I forgot about
the morning and Elsa Tablo,
it was a girl in Greece, and I
was a girl who loved to meditate
and do yoga
[music] you
can't say it,
I decided then I will pay for all
my friends to teach them yoga and
meditation
and I think that it was very clear for
me for me the seed for those studying now
my life I have the
best incense he took good morning
everyone good morning
thank you for editing together it
was like the story of a super agent I had
different jobs and different whale of responsibilities
and my meditation began with the fact that I seemed to be in a
cave
somewhere in the mountains and then I wanted to see
paradise living paradise
goal or but then I realized that beyond the mountains
live people who suffer greatly
I then just decided to give it all up and
go through the mountains and took a pilgrim like this
and began to walk from village to village
beyond the mountains behind these and I discovered there are
different cities
different different
people and I just did some kind of bad
work you know that's as if I  I
came to the airport and I carried luggage for
people who go to the
airport and arrive late for the
plane.
I also tried to help them in their homes, like I
worked as a plumber, tried to clean the
pipes, and so on. I also had
various
other jobs. I did this because
I wanted to see people happy.
I think this is a karmic correlation
to see angels who help other
people develop and meet their
teacher.
[music]
[applause]
okay, let's do the exchange to the toilet,
let's see each other in 10-15 minutes
and then we'll do lam rim, let's continue.